欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
嘿 卡尔文 你说想给我看样东西
Hey, Calvin. You said you wanted to show me something?
是 戴夫 是有
Yes, Dave, I do. Um...
看这个
Look at this.
这什么啊
What is it?
是换尿布台
It's the baby- changing table
就是你和珍玛送给蒂娜庆祝她奶奶洗礼的礼物
that you and Gemma gave Tina for her grandma shower.
上面写着“需要些许组装”
It says"some assembly required. "
这可不是些许 这全都得自己动手装
Well, this is not some. This is all.
卡尔文 这也是吸引人的部分呀
Well, Calvin, that's part of the appeal.
不仅是礼物 还是个有意思的建筑课题
Not only is it a gift, but it's a fun building project.
懂 都懂
I see. I get it.
你想我帮你装
You want me to help you build it.
接近了 我是想你来装
Close. I want you to build it
我去打高尔夫
while I go play golf.
这还真是个有意思的课题呢
Hmm, this is a fun project.
欢迎来到街区 欢迎来到社区
®Welcome to the block, welcome to the neighborhood*
欢迎跟我做邻居
Welcome to the hood.
蒂娜 你紧张不
So, Tina, are you nervous?
我们马上就知道你孙辈的性别啦
We're about to find out the sex of your grandchild.
错 是你马上就知道了
No, you re about to find out.
我的直觉几个月前就告诉我马蒂和考特尼
My instincts told me what Marty and Courtney
会发生什么事了 我来只是等着说一句
were having months ago. I'm just here to say,
早跟你说了吧”
"I told you so! "
瞧瞧 姑娘 你
Oh, oh, look at you, girl. You- -
都凸出来了呢
You just popped outta there!
瞧瞧
Lookit.
大家都这么说
So I keep hearing.
嘿 嘿 爸
Hey, uh, hey, Dad,
考特尼对自己体型有点敏感
Courtney is a little bit sensitive about her size.
好 明白 了解 没问题
Oh, oh, okay, got it, understood, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
丫头 瞧瞧
Girl, look at you!
这大体格子
As big as you wanna bel
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿 考特尼 过来坐一下吧
Hey, uh, Courtney, um, why don't you come have a seat?
好
Okay.
不是 不是
Oh, no. No, uh
坐这个结实点的
One of the more sturdy ones.
就是这样
There we go.
好 开始吧
All right, let's do it.
好
Okay.
无人机 起飞
Drones, up.
好 各位 表演时间到
Okay, folks, it's showtime.
请讲目光投向空中
Keep your eyes on the skies
一切即将揭晓
and all will be revealed.
我知道性别
I- I know the gender,
你能换成揭晓宝宝名字吗
can you reveal the baby's name instead?
妈 不可以
Mom, no.
我们不会透露姓名的
We're not telling anyone the name.
我们想留点悬念等生产那天再说
We want to save something for the big day.
行吧 我知道了你说得对
Okay. I know. You're right.
告诉我
Just tell mel
妈咪 不行
Mommy, no!
好 按吧
Okay. Hit it.
哪种性别是绿色
What gender is green?
你干嘛呢 戴夫
What are you doing, Dave?
我要用我的无火机拍性别揭晓
I'm gonna use my drone to film the gender reveal.
你真觉得我们会想再看一遍这个吗
You really think we're gonna want to watch this again?
无人机是在天空中拼成图案呢吗
Are the drones forming shapes in the sky?
是的 那个是猎户座
Yep. That's Orion.
那个是仙后座
A- And that's Cassiopeia.
你知道现在湖人队有比赛吧
You do know there's a Laker game on, right?
我喜欢 好有创意
I love it. It's so creative.
我虽然不理解 完全不理解 但还是很喜欢
I don't understand it, like, at all, but still.
开始啦
Here we go.
揭晓答案的时刻到啦
The moment of truth has arrived.
好 我把无人机就位
Okay,let me just get my drone in position...
是女孩
It's a girl.
早跟你说了吧
I told you so!
性别揭晓就这么草草收场了
Well, so much for our big gender reveal.
我们连最精彩的部分都没等到
And we didn't even get to the best part.
是呀
I know,
X和Y染色体在卵字上会合
where the X and Y chromosomes
那幕都没表演出来
converge on the ovum.
是
Yeah, well
至少将来我们有有意思的故事讲给佩内洛普听了
at least we'll have a fun story to tell Penelope someday.
戴夫 听好
Dave, listen.
如果你发现我举止怪异
If you notice I'm acting weird,
不要大惊小怪
don't make a big deal.
好
Okay.
我知道了一些
I've got some information
我不该知道的信息
that I shouldn't have
而这消息真的很棒
and it's really fantastic information,
可我不能告诉你 所以别来烦我
but I can't tell you, so leave me alone.
我觉得我能修好这个
You know, I think I can fix this.
戴夫 我知道马蒂和考特尼的宝宝叫什么了
Dave, I know the name of Marty and Courtney's baby.
-真的吗 你知道了 -是啊
Ooh, really, you do? Yeah.
叫什么呀
Well, what is it?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you!
虽然很想 但不能说
I'm dying to, but I can't.
他们把这事保密的
They're keeping it a secret.
好吧
Okay, well,
你是要尊重他们的意愿
you do need to respect their wishes.
要吗
Do I?
你是我老公 这算是个漏洞吧
I mean, you're my husband, it's kind of a loophole.
这倒是
That is true.
已婚人士内部无所不说
Married people do share everything.
可你不能跟别人说
But you can't tell anybody.
我跟谁说去啊
Well, w- who am I gonna tell?
叫佩内洛普
It's Penelope.
很好听啊
Oh, that's cute.
可以叫她“佩妮”或者“内莉”或者
She could by"Penny"or"Nelly"or- -
我知道了
Ooh, I know.
菠萝
Pineapple.
没人会叫她菠萝的
No one is gonna call her Pineapple.
我就打算这么叫她
Well, that's what I'm going to call her.
嘿 大家好呀
Hey, y'all.
-嘿 -嗨
Hey. Hi.
好 就为这个诡异的
Okay, do we really have to write
婴儿摇篮挂饰我们也得写张感谢卡吗
a thank- you card for this creepy crib mobile?
-好丑啊 -是啊
It is so ugly. Yeah.
谁会送这个给我们啊
Who even gave this to us?
我送哒
It's from me.
谢谢
Thank you.
我刚才没从婴儿角度来看它
You know, I wasn't looking at it from the baby's perspective, cosI
其实还挺好看的
it's actually beautiful.
比赛怎么样啊
So, how was the game?
嗯
Yeah...
我们赢了 但进到了加时赛
Well, we won, but it went into extra innings
而我还没开始写我的地质学论文
and I haven't even started writing my geology paper
论文明天就要交了
and it's due tomorrow.
地质学第一课
Ah. Geology 101,
想偷懒就学地质学
"rocks for jocks. "
那门课太简单了
That class was a piece of cake.
对我来说是的
Well, at least for me. medela
做个引体向上呗
Do a pull- up.
你不能每次争论什么都用这句话赢我
You can't win every argument like that.
你知道你能做什么吗 如果你想节省时间
You know what you could do? If you want to save time,
-找人工智能啊 -对
use AI. Yeah.
让它帮我写论文吗
Whoa, to write my paper?
不行 那就是作弊了
No way, that's cheating.
我想自己写
I want to write this myself.
拥抱未来 马尔科姆
Embrace the future, Malcolm.
以前人们还认为计算器是作弊呢
People used to think calculators were cheating.
还有拼写检查
And spell- checkers.
现在我们认为是理所当然
And now we take them for granted.
-现在你可以把人工智能当做理所当然（花岗岩） -是
And now you can take AI for granite. Yeah.
音同意不同
Gran- ite.
岩石
The rock.
是
Yeah.
这可怜娃娃投错胎子啊
This poor kid will be born stuffed in a locker.
天
Man.
嘿 戴夫
Hey, Dave.
-怎么样了啊 -还不错
How's it going? Not bad.
看
Check it out.
花这么长时间 就装了个这
All this time, that's it?
条腿
One leg?
我把D腿销钉装A腿上了
Well, I put the dowel for the D leg in the A leg.
然后 锁定支架的时候我用了长螺钉A
Then, I used long screw A in the locking bracket
而实际上我应该用短螺栓C 所以
when I was supposed to use short bolt C, so...
我不得不重新开始
I had to start over.
你确定那条腿装对了
Are you sure that leg is right?
确定
Yes.
确定吧
: Yes.
让一边去 我来
Step aside. I'm taking over.
我才不会把我的可爱小孙女
I'm not gonna put my sweet little grandbaby
放到你这纸牌屋上
on your house of cards.
你笑什么
What are you smiling about?
我在想你的可爱小孙女
I was just thinking about your sweet little grandbaby.
我不喜欢这笑容 戴夫 出什么事了
I hate smiles, Dave. What's going on?
没事啦 我只是
No, it's nothing, I just- -
有件关于她的事 我知你不知
I know something about her that you don't know.
我都不知道 你怎么会知道的
How would you know if I don't know?
我说得够多了
Look, well, I've said too much.
不许走 有史以来第一次
Oh, no, for the first time ever,
此言差矣
not true.
好吧 是这样
Okay, look,
珍玛让我保密
Gemma swore me to secrecy,
可你是我最好的朋友
but you are my best friend
而且如果有漏洞的话
and if there's any loophole,
也是指可以对你最好的朋友讲
it's for your BFF.
是是是 如果必须要付出这种代价 行吧
Yeah, yeah, you know, if that's what it takes, absolutely.
最好的朋友 可以
BFF, yeah.
宝宝名字
The baby's name
叫佩内洛普
is Penelope.
佩内洛普
Penelope.
好吧 行吧 挺好听的 我喜欢
Okay, yeah, that's cute. I like that.
对吧 我敢说我们很多人
Yeah, right? You know, I bet a lot of us
都会叫她菠萝
are gonna call her Pineapple.
我一直都很喜欢这个名字
You know, I- I've always liked that name.
中学时候我有一同学就叫佩内洛普
I knew a Penelope in middle school.
好 拜托 你可什么都别说啊
Oh. All right, well, please, you can't say anything.
珍玛会杀了我的
Gemma will kill me.
好 听好 我肯定守口如瓶
AlI right, look, your secret's safe with me.
好 谢了兄弟 对了
AII right, thanks, buddy. And by the way,
祝你组装柜子好运
good luck on the cabinet.
这是说明书
Here are the instructions.
戴夫 我可是大老爷们 不需要说明书
Dave. I'ma man, I don't need no damn instructions.
好吧
Okay, uh
这个人工智能网站我该从哪入手
Where do I start with this AI site?
看起来真的很复杂
This looks really complicated.
给我写一篇关于火成岩的三页的论文
Write me a three- page paper about igneous rocks.
好 怎么可能
Okay, how is that possibly- -
搞定
And done.
不可能 这东西怎么可能
No way. There's no way this thing
两秒钟就写出一篇好论文
can write a good paper in two seconds.
这也
This is.
该死
Oh, damn.
我们去吃寿司吧
Let's go get some sushi.
不行啊 马蒂 我不能就这么交上去
No, no, Marty, I can't just turn this in.
我希望这篇文章有我的努力在里面
I want this work to be my own.
行吧 就把人工智能写出来的东西
Oh. Okay, well, take what AI wrote
傻瓜化一下
and then dumb it down.
马尔科姆改良
Malcolm it up.
-嘿 宝儿 -怎么 -看下这个
Hey, babe. Check it out. Yeah?
我就是这方面的艺术家
I'm an artist with this thing.
单手搞定
One- handed.
后手掏
Behind the back.
蒙眼
Blindfolded.
好吧 这个有点没钻好
Okay, that was a little off right there.
优选刚送来了最可爱的粉色连体衣
Well, Prime just delivered the cutest pink onesies,
围兜 袜子 毛衣 连粉色尿布套都有
bibs, socks, sweaters, even pink diaper covers.
我还买了刺绣机
I've got the embroidery machine
可以把宝宝名字都给绣上去
to put the baby's name on all of them.
我现在没有的就是名字
What I don't have is the name.
保密也算是种传统 对不对
Well, I mean, keeping it secret is kind of a tradition, right?
更可以说是迷信
More like superstition.
我还以为他们不会这么守旧呢
You know, I thought they'd be smarter than that.
一个认为把手袋放地上
Says the woman who thinks we'll go broke
我们就会破产的女人竟然会说出这话
if you put your purse on the floor.
-我们破产了吗 -没啊
Are we broke? No.
不客气
You're welcome.
我可是奶奶哎
You know, I'm the grandmother.
我应该比任何人都早知道 对吧
I should know before anybody, right?
是 太 太扯了
Right. That's...That's crazy.
卡尔文·热罗尼莫·巴特勒
Calvin Geronimo Butler,
你是知道点什么吗
do you know something?
容我狡辩
Listen. Oh.
当某人告诉你个秘密
When somebody tells you a secret, Uh- huh.
他们是希望你告诉你配偶的 你不觉得吗
they expect you to tell your spouse, don't you think?
是 是希望 继续 说下去
Yeah, they do, they do, move on, move on.
所以 所以 好
So, so, so...AlI right, so,
这事你不能说出去 只能你知我知
you have to keep this just between us.
-好吗 -当然了 宝儿
AII right? Of course, baby.
好
AIl right.
戴夫说珍玛听到
So, Dave says Gemma heard
马蒂说
Marty say...Uh- huh.
宝宝名字是佩内洛普
...that the baby's name is Penelope.
佩内洛普
Penelope.
很好听对不对
It's cute, right?
我知道你会觉得好听
I know you think it's cute.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
得了吧 卡尔文
Oh, come on, Calvin.
佩内洛普
Penelope?
你第一任女友的名字
The name of your first girlfriend?
那会儿才七年级
That was seventh grade.
她算不上是我女朋友啦
And she was hardly my girlfriend.
净瞎想
You wild.
所以你跟一个都算不上是
So you had hot and heavy make out sessions
女朋友的女生热吻
with a girl that wasn't even your girlfriend?
就亲了那么一回
It was one kiss.
我接受不了
You know, I can't, I can't,
我没办法把
I cannot embroider
你亲过嘴的第一个女生的名字
these adorable pink baby clothes
绣到这些可爱的粉色婴儿衣服上
with the name of the first girl you slobbed down.
佩内洛普
Penelope.
这是我姨奶奶希拉送的
Oh, that's from my great aunt Sheila.
我都不知道塔吉特百货还卖五美元礼品卡呢
I didn't know Target sold five- dollar gift cards.
嘿 马蒂 嘿 考特尼 嘿
Oh, hey, Marty, hey, Courtney. Hey.
我想跟你们说件事
Um, well, I wanted to tell you something,
我知道轮不到我来讲 我也从没干涉过
and I know it's not my place, and I never meddle.
妈 你能直接跳到你要干涉的那部分吗
Mom, can you just skip to the part where you meddle?
好 我对宝宝的名字很有意见
Okay, well, I have a real problem with the baby's name.
不可以起那个名字
It's not gonna work.
我们还没跟人说宝宝叫什么呢
We haven't told anybody the baby's name.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
好吧 这
Okay, this is...
这事对我来说有点难以启齿
This is a little painful for me to talk about.
我们从没告诉过你
We never told you
或者你哥 几年前
or your brother, but years ago,
你父亲和别人有染
your father was involved with someone.
他们相爱了
They were in love.
天
Oh, my God.
是 那时候他读七年级
Yeah. It was when he was in the seventh grade.
先说这句不行吗
Well, then, lead with that.
你到底怎么了
What is wrong with you?
重点是
Well, the point is,
她叫佩内洛普 这决不能是
her name was Penelope and that cannot be
我孙女的名字
the name of my grandbaby!
我们不会叫宝宝佩内洛普的
Um, we re not naming our baby Penelope.
不会
No.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
你愿意为我这么做
You would do that for me?
谢谢
Thank you.
不是啊 本来也不叫佩内洛普
No. It was never Penelope.
只是在我们知道宝宝是女孩之前
That's just what we started calling the baby
给孩子起的名字
before we knew it was a girl.
真的吗
Really?
是 佩内洛普是我们的小玩笑
Yes. Penelope was just our little joke.
是啊
: Yeah.
我懂了
I get it, I get it.
这么叫很有意思因为这么难听的名字
It's funny because it's an ugly name
只适合额头超大的人
for people with big- ass foreheads.
我看过她年鉴上的照片
I looked at her yearbook picture.
真不敢相信你认为她会叫这名字
I- I cannot believe you thought that was the name.
现在没人叫佩内洛普这名字了
What- - there are no new Penelopes.
而且听起来很好笑
And it would sound ridiculous.
佩内洛普·普里金
"Penelope Pridgeon"?
普里金 普里金 这是 你的姓啊
Pridgeon. Pridgeon. That- - well, that's your last name.
-是啊 -好吧
Yeah. Okay. Okay.
好吧好吧
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay- - well,
我本以为是巴特勒 但是 这样也行
I- I was thinking Butler, but, you know, that- that's okay,
因为 我们没结婚
'cause you kn- - we're not married.
这么一说就合理了
Mm. Mm. Makes more sense.
对对对 嘿 女权主义
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Hey, this is what
就是要这样
a feminist looks like.
很好 亲
Well, that's great, honey.
是这样 我有很多
Well, you know what? I've got a ton
要绣的东西 但是
of embroidering to do, but...
等等 我没法绣 因为还不知道名字
Wait, I can't, because I still don't know the name.
我就想着可以 绣我想的名字
I guess Ican, you know, embroider names I think of.
我先从阿比盖尔绣起
Let me just start with Abigail?
阿格尼丝 阿玛雅
Agnes, Amaya...
-是达芬妮 -达芬妮 我喜欢
It's Daphne. Oh, Daphne! I love it!
好 妈 妈
MARTY: Okay, but Mom? Mom?
麻烦记住 这是秘密 所以请别告诉任何人
Please remember, it's a secret, so don't tell anyone.
不会不会 当然不会了
No, no, no, of course, of course.
达芬妮 的啊达
Daphne. D- A...
芬妮
P- H- N- E.
别跟我这儿抖机灵 孩子
Don't get smart with me, boy.
不得不说啊 卡尔文
I got to hand it to you, Calvin.
这看起来很棒啊
This- this looks great.
必须的 不看说明书 也不拖拖拉拉
Yup. No instructions, no dilly- dallying.
纯凭一股子力气 肌肉 还有电钻
Just power, muscle and a drill.
天
Oh, man.
怎么
What?
这怎么回事
Well, what's this?
怎么了
What?
这个弹出抽屉
The pop- out drawer.
弹不出来啊
It...it doesn't pop out.
-我看看好吧 -好
Let me see, okay? Yeah.
这不就成了 弹出来了
Okay, there it is. It popped out.
行吧
Yeah. Okay.
显然
Clearly,
如果我想把这个弄好 就得自己动手了
if I want this done right, I'm going to have to do it myself.
你把说明书还有我的
Now, where'd you put the instructions
小内六角扳手放哪儿了
and my little Allen wrench?
垃圾桶里
In the garbage
你运气好 有我这个最好的朋友
You know, you are lucky that you're my best friend.
嘿 嘿 达芬妮
Hey. Oh, hey, Daphne.
戴夫
Dave.
你刚说什么
What'd you say?
碰个拳 戴夫
Dap me, Dave.
真的吗
Really?
当然
Yeah.
行的吧
AlI right. Oh
-没问题 -是
That's cool. Yeah.
嘿 宝儿
Hey, baby.
Hey, babe. Mwah.
所以你不再为佩内洛普的事生气了
So you aren't mad about Penelope anymore?
拜托 都过去式了
Oh, please. That's in the past.
真的
Really?
不好意思啊 蒂娜 我不知道该如何表达
Uh, forgive me, Tina. I don't know how to say this.
但你什么时候变得这么通情达理了
But when did you become so reasonable?
我刚得知了一件能改善我心情的事
Well, I just found out something that improved my mood.
可我不能告诉你
But I can't tell you.
别这样啊
Whoa. Come on!
宝儿 我都告诉你了 还记得吗
Babe, I told you my thing, remember?
已婚夫妇的漏洞
The married couple loophole?
好吧 宝贝 但这可是大事
Okay, baby, but this is a big one.
宝宝名字不叫佩内洛普
Okay, the baby's name is not Penelope.
是达芬妮
It's Daphne.
好吧 可以
Okay. Yeah.
达芬妮·巴特勒
Daphne Butler.
行 也挺好听的
Okay, yeah, it's got a nice ring to it.
不 不是达芬妮·巴特勒 达芙妮·普里金
No, not Daphne Butler. Daphne Pridgeon.
普里金是谁
Who the hell is Pridgeon?
是考特尼的姓
It's Courtney's last name.
行吧 那跟我孙女有什么关系
Okay, so what that got to do with my grandbaby?
这是马蒂和考特尼决定的
It's what Marty and Courtney decided.
你得学会别管别人家的事
You got to learn. how to stay out of other people's business.
卡尔文
Well, Calvin,
你没把说明书扔垃圾桶里
you did not throw the instructions in the garbage.
你给扔到我堆肥桶里了 现在我的虫子都吓坏了
You threw em in my compost, and now my worms are freaking out.
你虫子关我屁事 戴夫
I don't give a damn about your worms, Dave.
巴特勒这名字要断代了
The Butler name is in jeopardy.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我本不该说 可我太生气了
Look, I'm not supposed to say anything, but I am too upset.
卡尔文 友情漏洞
Calvin, friendship loophole.
说来听听
Spill the tea.
宝宝名字叫达芙妮·普里金
The baby's name is Daphne Pridgeon.
-普里金是谁 -谢谢
Who the hell's Pridgeon? Thank you!
珍玛 我有个不能告诉你的
Gemma, I have a huge secret
大秘密
I can't tell you.
婚姻漏洞
Marriage loophole.
好哒 那我别无选择
Ooh. Okay, then, I have no other choice.
宝宝名字不是佩内洛普
The baby's name is not Penelope.
是达芙妮
It's Daphne.
好可爱哦
Oh, that's cute.
对吧 达芙妮·普里金
Right? Daphne Pridgeon.
普里金是谁
Who the hell is Pridgeon?
是考特尼 卡尔文可难受了
It's Courtney, and Calvin is crushed.
肯定的啊
Oh, I bet.
他怎么知道的
How did he even find out?
你跟我说孩子名字叫佩内洛普
Well, you told me the name Penelope,
我可能就告诉了卡尔文 他又告诉了蒂娜
and Imay have told Calvin, who told Tina,
蒂娜告诉了马蒂 马蒂跟蒂娜说了孩子真名
who told Marty, who told Tina the baby's actual name.
她回来告诉卡尔文 卡尔文又告诉我 现在我在跟你讲
She told Calvin, who told me, and now I'm telling you.
看看你家兄弟 我拿了A
Check out your boy. I got an A.
好吧
: Okay. All rightl
我就说人工智能是正确的选择
I told you AI was the way to go.
没有 我自己写的
Uh, no, no, I wrote that myself.
完全没有用到人工智能
I didn't use AI at all.
你还拿个A 还是科学学科
And you got an A...in a science class?
你不信我
You don't believe me.
我跟你说 都是我自己写的 马蒂
I'm telling you, that's all me, Marty.
是 我刚还做了个俯卧撑呢
Oh, yeah, sure, and I just did a push- up.
叩叩
Knock, knock.
请进
Come in?
马蒂 你爸因为件事有点不开心
Marty, your dad is upset about something,
他之所以知道的唯一原因是我大嘴巴
and the only reason he knows is'cause of my big mouth.
什么事啊
What is it?
你孩子会姓
It's killing him
普里金这事让他难受死了
that your baby's last name is going to be Pridgeon.
普里金是谁啊
Who the hell is Pridgeon?
你们认识我多久了
How long have you people known me?
好了 各位 我们得谈一下
AlI right, everybody, we need to talk.
我们知道我们宝宝的情况有点不寻常
We understand our baby situation is unconventional.
我们很开心你们都非常兴奋
And we love that you are all super excited.
是的 是的 很开心
MARTY: We do. We do. We love it.
但我们不大喜欢你散播谣言
But what we love less is you guys spreading rumors
背后八卦我们的选择这种行为
and gossiping about our choices.
珍玛挑的头
Gemma started it.
什么
What? l
我只告诉了戴夫 这是婚姻漏洞 大家都知道的呀
Just to Dave. It's the marriage loophole, everybody knows it.
是 就跟最好朋友漏洞一样
Yeah, just like the best friend loophole. Yeah.
就没这说法
That's not a thing.
好吧 可以
Okay, willwill?
你们可不可以
Will you please
让我们说
let us talk?
现在我们正式宣布宝宝名字
We are now officially going to announce our baby's name. Mm.
正式不再是个秘密
Well, it's officially not a secret.
是达芙妮
It's Daphne.
金小姐在杂货店告诉我了
Miss Kim told me at the grocery store.
我们宝宝的名字是达芙妮
Our baby s first name will be Daphne.
她的姓
Her last name
则会是普里金－巴特勒
will be Pridgeon- Butler.
好 非常感谢 二位
Oh. Okay. Thank you so much, guys.
这太棒了
This is awesome.
这个名字 传承继续下去了
The name, the legacy continues.
有没有可能改成巴特勒－普里金
Is there any chance that you can go Butler- Pridgeon?
-怎么了 不行吗 -见好就收 宝儿
What? No? Take the win, baby.
蒂娜 准备好被迷住 接下来向你展示
Tina, prepare to be dazzled. May I present to you
史密的朱诺五号豪华换尿布桌
the Juno Five Deluxe Changing Table by Smim.
真是目眩神迷 我很喜欢
I am dazzled. I love it.
是呢 碰一下
Yeah. Dap.
咱们之间的互动嘛
Huh? It's our thing.
是
Oh, yeah.
跟我当初做的那个一模一样
This looks exactly the same as when I did it.
是 不过有一点关键的不同
Yes, except, for one crucial difference.
这个能用 蒂娜
It works. Tina?
何不试一下弹出式尿布抽屉
Why don't you take the pop- out diaper drawer
抽屉带缓冲闭合机制的哦
with soft- close mechanism for a ride?
好的 好的 我看下哈
Okay, okay. Let me see.
不错哎
Ah. Okay. Huh?
太棒了
It's spectacular.
很厉害 戴夫
I'm- I'm impressed, Dave.
我都等不及把臭臭的小宝宝
I just can't wait to put a stinky little baby
放到这家伙上面了
up on this bad boy.
好吧 我不得不承认 戴夫
Yeah, I got to admit, Dave.
我以为你做不到呢
I didn't think you could do it.
对你一点信心都没有
I had no faith.
丁点都无 零
Absolutely none. Zero.
如果你看后面这里
Oh, and if you look back here,
这些带子能起到防地震功能
these straps make it earthquake- safe.
是
Yeah.
格罗弗 你拼的是吗
Grover, did you build this?
是的先生 我看了些油管视频
Yes, sir. II watched some YouTube videos.
20分钟才装完
It took me 20 minutes.
格罗弗 当初说好了是秘密
Grover, we agreed it was a secret.
是 但是你忘了
Yeah, but you forgot
“我害怕卡尔文先生”这个漏洞啊
about the"I'm scared of Mr. Calvin" loophole.